<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Derya Yavuz Ionescu</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Derya Yavuz Ionescu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.152.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:44:59 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My OSCP Journey</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/oscp_study/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:44:59 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/oscp_study/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;oscp-preparation-revisited-in-2025&#34;&gt;OSCP Preparation Revisited in 2025&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back at a stressful year&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to write this because the OSCP was genuinely one of the hardest things I’ve done in my career so far, especially considering where I started - as I had comparably less knowledge than my peers when I began working as a security engineer. When I had obtained the OSCP, I had been in the field for a year and a half, but I learned everything on the job, through real client work, mistakes, panic, and figuring things out as I went.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a CPTC Practice Range Environment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:15:59 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the purposes of training our team for the Collegiate Penetration Team Competition (CPTC) for the 2025-2026 season, as team captain, I was facing the challenge of providing an accurate laboratory range environment that the team could potentially face during the competition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luckily, my awesome friends ran to my help and all of us together began the planning and building process of out CPTC mock competition range - our goal was to accurately convey a potential modern customer environment with a variation of Windows and Linux servers and other applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
